I dyed my hair.
髪染めた
Did you dye your hair?
髪染めた?
I dyed my hair.
髪染めた
nice.
いいね
I did it.
やった
It suits you, right?
似合ってるでしょ
difficult.
難しい
happy.
嬉しい
The uniform is nice too.
制服もいいね
If you bring it.
持ってくれば
Oh, my uniform?
あ、私制服?
Indeed, certainly.
確かに確かに
copper?
どう?
What have you been up to lately?
最近何してたの?
I was working part-time.
バイトしてた
Did you have a part-time job?
バイトしてた?
Yeah.
うん
It was difficult.
大変だった
Are you studying?
勉強してる?
study.
勉強
I did it.
しちゃった
Did you do it?
しちゃった?
nice.
いいね
Did you get your bangs done?
前髪なんか揃えた?
Aligned.
揃えた
That's good.
いいよね
I understand.
分かる
close.
近い
I want to see it up close.
近くで見たい
I thought I'd take it easy today.
今日はゆっくりしようかなと思って
I received a hand.
手貰いました
Thank you for coming.
ありがとうね、来てくれて
You took it easy, right?
ゆっくりしたでしょ?
i want to sleep.
寝たい
What, do you want to sleep?
え、寝たい?
why?
なんで?
sleepy.
眠たい
lie?
嘘?
Oh, my friend.
あ、友達が
A friend.
友 達が
Why is that okay?
なんでいいの?
It's right below.
すぐ下でしょ
Take a look.
ちょっと見て
yeah?
ん?
do not have.
ない
amazing.
すごい
cute.
かわいい
Looks great.
えらしい
I'm beautiful.
私、綺麗だね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Look, look, look.
見て見て見て
Squat down and look.
しゃがんで見て
I wonder what this is.
なんだろう、これ
terrible.
やばい
I'm putting something in there.
何か入れてる
Do you think you can put it in?
入れてそう?
Check it.
確認して
Was there something in it?
何か入ってた?
There's nothing in it.
何も入ってない
Wasn't it in?
入ってなかった?
There's nothing in it.
何も入ってない
Ho
ほ
Look, look.
ら、 見て
Look at the camera, look.
カメラ見ながら、ほら
Let's compare it with the face.
顔と、じゃあ比べてほら
delicious?
おいしい?
Yeah.
うん
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てほら
terrible.
やばい
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Isn't it red?
赤くない?
cute.
かわいい
No, boobs.
ダメだよ、おっぱい
I hate breasts.
嫌い、おっぱいですね
I can't stand this.
我慢できない、これ
Oh, wow, look.
あ、すごい、ほら
My face stinks.
顔が臭いもんで
Shoes, too.
靴もね、ほら
Okay, okay.
よしよしよし
Aren't you going to sleep?
寝てこない?
Okay, okay.
よしよし
terrible.
やばい
rise
起
What happened?
こ った?
It's bad, it's really bad.
やばい、マジでやばい
Is it cute at all?
全然かわいいの?
Oh no, I got a pimple, no way.
やばい、ニキビできちゃった、やばい
Well, I'll take a quick shower next time.
じゃあ次一回ちょっとシャワーね
Shall we eat?
食べよっか
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
Oh no.
やば
I wasn't even wearing shoes.
靴も履いてなかったからね
Oh, were you drinking water?
お、水飲んでた?
Oh, I was drinking water.
お、水飲んでた
Was it because I was surprised?
びっくりしたから?
I was surprised.
びっくりした
It's cute.
かわいいね
Is it cute now?
可愛くなりました?
It's not getting any cuter.
可愛くなってないですよ
I just drank again.
今、また飲んだよ
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しいでしょ
What are you doing now?
今何してるんだっけ?
I'm studying now.
今勉強してる
Are you studying?
勉強してる?
What are you studying?
何の勉強?
Studying for the exam.
受験勉強
Ah, I see.
あ、 そっか
So, you graduated from high school?
あれ、高校卒業したんだっけ?
I graduated from high school.
高校卒業した
University entrance exam.
大学受験
Old life.
老人生
It's an old life.
老人生なんだね
How are you studying?
どうですか、勉強は?
Mathematics is difficult to study and I've been lazy lately.
勉強は、数学は難しくて、最近怠けてる
Mathematics is difficult, isn't it?
数学難しいよね
Summer is already over, and there are things like patterning.
もう夏も終わって、模糸とかあったね
It was there, it was there.
あったあったあった
The pattern was a little good.
模糸はちょっと良かった
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
Good judgment.
判定が良かったね
It was good, it was good.
良かった良かった
Build your confidence.
自信つくくね
I feel like I can go.
いけるって感じ
Which school do you want to go to now?
今、志望校はどこなんだっけ?
Well, I thought I wanted to go to Seigaku,
まあ、青学行きたいなって思ってたけど、
I started aiming for the national school rate.
ちょっと国校率目指し始めた
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
why?
なんで?
Hmm, what can I say?
う ーん、なんて言うんだろう
I'm not good at math, so I wanted to add some more subjects.
数学苦手だから、何か科目増やして、
I think it's better that way.
そっちの方が良いなーみたいな
I see, strategic.
なるほどね、戦略的な
Yes, strategically.
そう、戦略的に
Well, okay, if you go here, I want you to go to university.
えー、いいじゃん、ここに行くと大学行ってほしい
Hey, I want to go.
ね、行きたい
You want to go to Seigaku too, right?
青学も行きたいんでしょ?
I wish I could go to Seigaku.
青学は行ければいいなーみたいな
It seems popular.
モテそうだね
Eh, then studying is really hard.
えー、じゃあ勉強すごい大変だね、
Right now.
今ね
Even though you're busy, I think you'll have to come over for something.
忙しいのに何か来てもらうと思うね
thank you.
ありがとう
Why did you come?
なんで来てくれたの?
I feel like I want to do something since I haven't done it recently.
なんか、最近してないから、したいなーみたいな
picture?
え?
It's like a little bit.
ちょっとしたいなーみたいな
What?
何を?
Amazing, true to desire.
すごい、欲望に忠実な
I don't really want to have sex with you.
あんまり、ヘッチしたいっていうね、
There's no one to tell me.
言ってくる子いないんだよ
It's erotic.
エロいんだね
Lately I've been doing it myself.
自分でしたりするんだ、最近は
I haven't been with anyone lately,
最近は、誰かとしたりしてないから、
sometimes.
たまに
I'm busy.
忙しいしね
It's like I want to touch you a little.
ちょっと触れ合いたいなーみたいな
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Hey, what kind of person do you like?
ちょっと、どういう人が好きですか?
What kind of person are you?
どういう人?
A manly person.
男らしい人
What do you think is manly?
どういうところが男らしいなーと思う?
Someone who can afford it.
余裕のある人
I can't afford it.
余裕なんて
It's like he's taking the lead.
リードしてくれるみたいな
Wow, you've found the right person.
すごいね、ぴったりの人材を
It's amazing, I like young kids.
すごいなんか、若い子が好きな
Who are you?
誰ですか?
cute.
かわいい
The real thing is terrible.
実物やばいね
Super cute.
超かわいい
It's real.
本物だ
Highest.
最高
I'm a fan.
ファンなんです
You were too late to name yourself.
名乗り遅かったね
I'm a fan, a fan.
ファンです、ファン
I'm your fan.
あなたのファンです
What do you mean?
何のこと?
Super cute.
超かわいい
Stand up for a moment.
ちょっと、立って
How cute.
何かわいい
It's real.
本物だー
That's amazing.
すごいね
Take a look here.
ちょっとこっち見て
Her butt is also really cute.
お尻もめっちゃかわいい
It's cute.
かわいいね
Highest.
最高
I'm so happy.
嬉しいなー
I finally met you.
やっと出会えた
It smells so good.
すっげーいい匂い
The reactions are cute too.
リアクションもかわいいね
I feel confused.
戸惑ってる感じ
I can't stand it.
たまんないですよ
Uncle, I love young and cute girls.
おじさんね、若くてかわいい子大好きなんで
You came today because you wanted to have sex because you said you haven't done it lately, right?
最近してないなーって言ってHしたくて今日来たんでしょ?
Wow, that's great.
うわー、最高だね
With my uncle.
おじさんとじゃ
Cute middle face.
中顔かわいい
Show me your insides.
中顔見せて
what up?
どうした?
Eyes.
目って
I touch it too much.
あんまり触っちゃうよ
This is what it is.
これってさ、あれだよね
One piece is connected, right?
1枚繋がってるんだよね
How do I remove it?
どうやって抜くの?
When you pull it out.
抜くとき
show me.
見せて
You can't see anything like this when you pull it out.
こんなの抜くときなんか見れないじゃん
Tsukebi is standing really well.
つけびすごい立ってるね
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいとこあるの?
here?
ここ?
Here?
ここか
It's here.
ここだ
That's honest.
素直だね
It doesn't work that way.
そういうふうにはいかないよ
Look at this elasticity.
見てこの弾力
It's almost shaking.
ほぼ揺れてるよ
Did you know?
知ってた?
Do you know?
知ってる?
Can it shake like this?
こんなに揺れること?
That's great.
最高だね
The armpits are so beautiful.
お脇めっちゃ綺麗
Do you want to go through it?
くぐったい?
TRUE?
本当?
Not much?
むちろくない?
Isn't the feeling of being ticklish just like that?
くすぐったいと気持ちって結構髪ひとりじゃない?
Your reaction is cute.
リアクションかわいいね
I'm just watching.
見てるだけだよ
Look carefully.
ちゃんと見て
So beautiful.
すげえ綺麗
I guess licking doesn't tickle me.
舐めんのくすぐったくないんだね
tickles.
くすぐったい
The sides are really delicious.
お脇めっちゃ美味しい
Your stocking legs are terrible.
ストッキング足やばいね
Doesn't it bite?
食い込まない?
this.
これ
It digs in.
食い込むよね
Look.
ほら
It's beautiful.
綺麗なんだ
I want to see your beautiful skin.
綺麗な肌をさ、見たいんだけど
It came out.
出てきた
Amazing white skin.
すげえ肌真っ白
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It keeps coming out.
どんどん出てくる
I've done this much.
こんなにしちゃった
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I wonder what he's doing.
何してるんだろうね
I want to see your skin.
肌が見たくてさ
See, more and more come out.
ほら、どんどん出てくるよ
It's smooth.
すべすべだね
The leg that came out.
出てきちゃった足
or
や
You're so sensitive.
っぱ りここ敏感だね
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Didn't you think I'd touch you?
触れると思ってなかった?
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
Where are you looking?
ど こ見てる?
I can't see it.
見えない
Do you know where I'm looking?
どこ見てるかわかる?
I don't know.
わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんないの?
Don't look.
見ないで
I'll see.
見るよ
Don't look.
見ないで
I'll really watch it.
めっちゃ見るよ
That's a beautiful butthole.
綺麗なお尻の穴だね
See, see.
見る見る
You can see the hole here.
穴がここで見るから
It was open from the beginning.
穴開いてたね、最初から
Soooo beautiful.
すっげー綺麗
There aren't many wrinkles, right?
シワがあんまないんじゃない?
This side remains.
こっち側、残ってる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
TRUE?
本当?
Has it already become like this?
もうすでにこんなになってるの?
Soooo beautiful.
すっげー綺麗
There's not a single stain.
シミ一つないじゃん
Seriously super beautiful skin.
マジで超綺麗な肌
This is my favorite.
これ一番好きなんだね
beautiful skin.
綺麗な肌
There's no bag.
袋ないね
picture?
え?
I've been looking in many places.
いろんなところ見てんだよ
Are you watching?
見てんの?
Yes, you're watching.
そう、見てんの
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's not tasty.
おいしくないよ
It's delicious.
おいしいよ
delicious.
おいしい
I don't need dinner tonight.
今夜晩飯いらないね、もう
Looks like a gravure idol.
グラビアアイドルみたいだね
With your feet in front of you.
足を前にして
Don't gravure idols pose like this?
グラビアアイドルってこういうポーズしない?
That's right, that's it.
そうそう、それそれ
Just do that.
ちょっとそれやってて
Is there actually no such thing as a gravure idol?
実はグラビアアイドルってことはないの?
No.
違うよ
Come into the good stuff.
いいものに入ってきて
Do you know this?
これ 知ってる?
I know.
知ってるんだ
Seriously?
マジか
I've never used it.
使ったことない
It's a microphone, right?
マイクでしょ?
microphone.
マイク
This is how you get in.
こうやって入るんだから
I've never used it.
使ったことない
Well, today is my first experience.
じゃあ 今日初体験だ
Ma
マ
Ji?
ジ?
You did it.
や ったね
Seriously?
マ ジか
I lost.
負けちった
TRUE?
本当?
Does this feel good too?
こっちも気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Wow, that's amazing.
うわー、すげー
Don't you say things like this?
こう いうこととかしないの?
I've never done it.
したことない
What did you imagine?
何想像したの?
I've never done that.
したことないよ
I've never done it.
したことないんだ
I think we can make friends here.
ここで友達にならそう
It's been a long time since I went here.
こっち行ったらもう長いね
What's the best part about it?
当たってるいいとこ?
Okay.
よし
Should I apply this directly?
これ直接当てたほうがいいかな?
What do you think?
どうなの?
apply directly.
直接当てる
Guess directly?
直接当てる?
That's honest.
素直だね
Because there's no hair.
毛がないからさ
I want to see something else.
他に見たいもんね
I want to see it.
見たい
difficult?
難しい?
I want to see your feet too.
足も見たいじゃん
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
please.
どう ぞ
Because it's kind of cute.
ちょっとかわいいから
It's so cute to be shy.
恥ずかしがってるのすげーかわいいよ
I'll hide it.
隠れちゃうんだね
He served it himself.
自分で出してくれた
Great great.
偉い偉い
It's a lot of fun.
すごいなりなりしてる中
It's so noisy.
うるせーわ
It's Teles.
テレスだね
Is it really good?
めっちゃいい?
this.
これ
Huh?
あれ?
My legs.
足が
It has become an anime.
アニメになってきた
I like Teles.
テレスは好き
Is this better?
こっちのほうがいい?
こ っちのほうがいい?
I won't be able to stand up.
立てなくなっちゃう
Why?
どうして?
I don't have any strength.
力が入んない
Does it feel good?
気持ちよくて?
Excuse me.
失礼した
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
What did you say was coming out?
何が出るって言ったの?
Looks like it's about to come out.
もう出ちゃいそう
Does it look like it's about to come out?
出ちゃいそう?
What?
何が?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Can you see this?
こっち見える?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
That feels good.
それ気持ちいいね
You're good at it.
上手だね
You can put out the bell and move.
ベル出して動きできる
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
That's amazing.
すごいね、それ
Erotic.
エロい
That's erotic.
エロいね
Yeah.
うん
Can I leave it out like this?
このまま出しちゃっていい?
I put out a lot.
いっぱい出しちゃった
It felt so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちよかったよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's nothing.
なんでもない
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I'll do it again.
またやるんで
I want to do it again.
またやりたいな
good?
いい?
Do it again.
またやって
I'm going crazy.
お か しく な っちゃう
Will it go crazy?
おかしくなっちゃう?
It's going to be weird.
おかしくなっちゃう
Since I can't do it, I usually have these breasts.
できないから、だいたいこのおっぱい
Hey, this.
ねぇ、これ
Me, I'm in the middle of washing.
俺ね、洗ってる途中
That's right, let's go wash it then.
そうだそうだ、じゃあ洗っていこうか
Yes, I wash it.
うん、洗う
I want to wash it.
洗いたい
Wash it, then wash it.
洗うか、じゃあ洗う
I'll wash it, please wait a moment.
洗うよ、ちょっと待ってね
Because I'm washing it.
俺が洗ってるから
Yeah, okay.
うん、 いいよ
What are you doing?
何やってんの?
that...
あの...
Not yet.
あ んな ってさ、まだね
hey.
ね
It was amazing just now.
さっきすごい済みましたじゃん
I always have boobs.
いつもおっぱいがさ
That's great.
最高だよね
I need to wash this one too.
こっちもね、こっちも洗わないとね
Legs like this.
足を、こうやって
Yes, that's right, raise your legs.
そうそうそう、足をね、上げてごらん
increase?
上げる?
Yeah.
うん
Wouldn't it wash better that way?
そんなほうがよく洗うでしょ?
Like this.
こうやって
Do it like this.
こう やって
How do you usually wash your clothes?
いつもどうやって洗ってんの?
Oh, let me show you how to wash it.
あ、ちょっと洗う方見せてよ
It's not normal.
普通はないよ
Normally, no, I don't really go all the way inside, right?
普通、いや、なんか、あんまりでも中までやんないんでしょ?
Yeah, it's like this.
うん、こんな感じ
Is that what it feels like?
そういう感じ?
surface?
表面?
Will it hurt if I go too far inside?
あんまり中までやると、痛めちゃう?
Oh, is this Gori?
あ、これゴリ?
real?
ほんと?
Did you cum just now?
さっき中出したの?
Yeah.
うん
Seriously?
マジか
Well, I'll let it flow for a while.
じゃあちょっと流すよ
Plenty of hot water.
お湯がたっぷり
Hey, nice.
ねえ、いいね
play.
弾く
You have really big boobs.
めっちゃおっぱいよ
The hot water is splashing.
お湯が弾いてるよ
Now that I'm washing my insides,
今さ、 sponsors 中まで洗っていると、
How about writing well?
よく書いては?
I have to wash the inside properly.
ちゃんと中まで洗わないとよ
Is it washed?
洗えてる?
this?
これ?
It's washed.
洗えてる
real?
ほんと?
I also wash myself on the altru stage.
この自分もさ、アルトルステージで洗う
Oh, oh, no, no.
え、あ、違う違う
Doesn't it come with that?
それ付かない?
No.
ダメだよ
Even if I sit down
座っても
What?
ら って
You're good at washing.
洗い方上手だね
It's going to get bigger.
大きくなっちゃう
Do this too.
こ っちもして
I agree.
そうだね
It's important.
大事だね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Female affairs?
女大事?
It's my first time.
初めてね
first time.
初めて
It's important, so today.
大 事 だね、じゃあ今日は
good?
いい?
It felt really good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかったよ
It made a bit of a loud noise, see you again.
ちょっと激しい音しちゃったね、またね
Okay, take your time and take a shower.
いいよ、ゆっくり、シャワー浴びて
thank you.
ありがとう
Good, it was great.
よかった、最高だった